The story deals with a minister's fall from grace through the wiles of the beautiful
concert hall singer, "Wild Honey" and the subsequent regeneration of both.
Wild Honey is a western film directed by Francis J. Grandon.
Actress Letty Noon and Rev.
David Warwick seek advice from a parson who tells the tale of a
minister who falls for a dance hall girl named Wild Honey.
After a jealous suitor frames the minister for murder, Wild
Honey clears his name, and he realizes her love.
When another suitor tries to shoot the minister,
Wild Honey is wounded protecting him.
The minister takes her to another town, and they live happily together.
Wild Honey, played by Doris Kenyon.
Rev. Jim Brown, played by Frank Mills.
Dick Hadding, played by Edgar Jones.
Joe Stacey, played by Jack Hopkins.
'Doc' Bliss, played by Howard Kyle.
Ed Southern, played by Henry Hebert.
Wild Honey is a 1918 silent film western directed by Francis J.
Grandon and starring Doris Kenyon.
The film is preserved in the archives of the Museum of Modern Art.